I can't meet them then. I'm in court.
我那会儿不能见他们.我要出庭.
You're in court the next day.
你在那之后第二天才出庭.
Right.
是的.
But I'm also in court on Wednesday.
但我周三也要出庭.
The next day is Wednesday.
第二天就是周三.
Trish, we just started and we're already out of sync.
Trish,我们才刚开始就已经节奏不同了.
I cannot have all these meetings.
我不能参加所有会议.
There aren't enough hours in the day.
白天没那么多时间.
With all due respect,
恕我直言,
you don't write things down in the calendar.
你不把事情写在日程表上.
So I don't know how full your schedule is,
所以我不知道你的安排究竟有多满,
which is why we still have these little meetings.
这就是我们还会有这些小会的原因.
Can we agree that the day after Wednesday is Thursday?
我们是否能一致同意周三之后是周四呢?
That's a joke, Trish. A little joke.
开个玩笑,Trish.一个小玩笑.
May we start from the beginning?
我们可以从头开始吗?
By all means.
当然可以.
The Credit Card Association would like to meet with you on Tuesday morning.
信用卡协会想在周二上午见你.
Fine. I can do it in the morning.
好的.可以在早上进行.
Afterwards, I'm in court.
然后我要出庭.
Fine. Which case?
好的.哪个案子?
People vs Kenton.
公众对Kenton.
That case doesn't start until next week!
这案子要到下周才开始.
We're talking about next week!
我们谈的就是下周的安排!
We're talking about this week!
我们谈的是本周的安排!
Trish, I said, "Let's talk about next week."
Trish,我说了,"让我们谈下周的安排."
You said it on Friday.
你是在上周五说的.
Last week, "next week" means "this week" this week.
上周说的"下周"到这周就变成"这周"了.
You're going to make a very good attorney.
你会成为一名出色的律师.